hi I'm here with Ally Bhusari co-founder
of pilot R&amp;D and render food hi Ally
thanks for coming thanks thanks for
having me great as you know you know
this class we talk about everything
related to food and the factors that go
into why you eat what you eat so I'm
hoping maybe you could just provide a
little introduction about what you do
and how it relates to the course in
general yeah so I the the field we call
it culinary science so technically I
think I'm a culinary scientist but we
made up the name so for whatever that's
worth and it's a blend of food science
and Jefferey I have been into science
since I was in high school and there was
a moment when I realized that I could
blend that with being a chef and for a
lot of reasons it's something that
didn't really happen a lot in previous
years of what food science was basically
it's attacking problems of how do you
make food different and delicious and
consistent using like a twin skill set
cool yeah and I know you majored in
biochemistry that was your original
major yeah yeah so did you start out
being interested in science or in food
and like how did how did these two come
together for you yeah food and science
were always in my head and in my life
and they found each other really
naturally so I come from a multi-ethnic
household so my dad was from Iran my
mom's from Central Texas so food was in
the conversation people like sweet
crispy crispy bits yeah yeah so if we're
looking for ways to be unified in life
one of the small ways that that can
start to happen with food is
appreciating that there's as diverse and
rich and varied as food is is really all
the same when you get down to a certain
level yeah and there's something
reassuring about that science will you
notice okay yeah yeah excellent thing
then done
thank you so much for coming I know
you're super busy and it was really fun
to talk food with you today yeah this
was a blast thank you