if you're a fan of Johnny Depp you may
remember this story last week he's known
as one of the nicest guys in Hollywood
but Johnny dad has excelled himself yes
the star donned his famous Jack Sparrow
pirate costume Australia to pay a visit
to a Children's Hospital well now more
video has been released of deps visit
and it's pretty cool now if there's
other people in it why do you call it a
selfie the Hollywood actor was
interviewed by 13 year old EULA price
Davies a leukemia patient at lady
Cilento Children's Hospital in Brisbane
what she said was his food you've ever
tasted grossest food a little possum
really but I thought they were cute and
fluffy not when we cooked the fall
interview appeared on juiced TV a
television show made by children at the
hospital
you