like the hokies rule ah you should
hahahaha that's good ha I'm glad your
palm good have to understand my carriage
is difficult to talk about and so far
he's not quite what you think he is
steamed chicken and steamed asparagus
this is it this is a diet to get you
know rip baby no I can I like dressing
up right best thing about being strong
um you get the lift ladies just like
that yeah like that when you in Budapest
did you just have kind of roaring
sessions and I felt like do you mean you
could give I did you know well that was
not even on my she tell you so much to
see hey y'all ready to your first kids
sorry we had some raw regions hey I mean
Reese Saturday's now for everybody at
home what is his muscles like can about
those they're all fake they're not even
real we pet we digitally put them on now
they are amazing I mean look at the
veins in his arms I mean they aren't
just the blood rushing through his veins
is amazing Bobby you would really Rory
kind is the best I was the best thing no
I'm not sorry go ahead i'm quite one
you're on your white luck with it to be
doing your interviews with such a
beautiful woman no I'm like you two to
make my interview with a little magic
yeah I judge a beautiful woman yeah
remember that's when we escape what it
over to my apartment I got people I dog
yeah I got bit by dog okay so now we
have in celebration of Hercules at that
wall let's do it are you ready yeah okay
one two three four I declare a thumb war
go okay
go and then we now have to like push
that you up the other person's the other
passes thumb down Oh q3 you're so good
at that like this one two three this is
go you just go like you're supposed to
push mine before I did you buy you one
puppy goodbye natural ah tag team oh oh
that was good so cheating you Barney at
Utah oh right okay see how draw you in
ah but I let you win uh and I came down
and down we did it wait don't leave me
hanging it is it is the best
you