hello Nina I'm Kendall and I'm with the
team effort itza I suppose it just means
that you have to be very dedicated I
think it's meant a lot of a lot of long
hours putting it on some time on the
weekends to make it happen on that note
I think the biggest tip that we kind of
learned over and over is that you also
have to care for yourself well and you
can't burn out early in the game or
there's no future so be sure to care for
your teammates and remind each other I
think to take breaks
I think uncertainty is a part when you
talk about a start up right away what
comes to my mind anyway is risk whether
it's successful or not is very dependent
on the work that you put in and also
environmental factors that are out of
your hands to some degree so so there's
definitely risk and yeah that that might
be the downside that I see but I think
it's definitely a risk worth taking
hello Nina I'm Karina and I'm one of the
cofounders of think you know
just do it
so we have spoken to a trademark lawyer
and has helped us with that first we
actually had a and another name at one
point and we realized that another Bank
in this city had trademarked it very
closely and that could have cost
potential problems the cool thing about
being a entrepreneur thing in general is
the flexibility and the ability to
create what you really believe in and
what you want to do and I think the cool
thing about being a tech startup is all
the opportunities and possibilities that
take allows us to do today that we could
never have imagined years ago and that
just makes it easier and faster for a
lot of startups to grow ask the customer
from the beginning on because then you
make something to customer image and
don't ask what they need ask what they
are doing where they have problems in
the during the day and something like
this because then you find out the real
problems of the customer we we have our
design thinking approach which was the
which gave us the prototype for the
product talked a lot with people
you can do what you want you don't have
to ask can I take this local a little
bit more on the right side or on the
left you just do it you can fail and
it's very important to fail because if
you fail you you learn a lot of