and anyone using them goddamn pitches
they used to picture some photographer
took a year ago with me with a straight
jacket on you know am I crazy
I was having concerts they were sold out
white boys Mexicans blacks and they
would do whatever I said I could tell
all those people audience to turn around
in a circle
and they would do it I was having love I
mean like undeniable love and I was
scared I was scared that I would come to
a town and I have the leader of the gang
they're telling me what do you need I
was scared but so is America so with
somebody else because all of a sudden I
had all kind of legal problems and you
have to think about this I had a clean
record for 20 years a clean record
living in the ghetto in the gutter no
record what about my morals then what
about my character then you know I'm
saying in two years that I start raising
New Orleans that I start being publicly
viewed I've had a record and now it
looks like I'm a criminal who has no way
of being reformed but all of these came
one after the other
do you understand it takes logic well
what about I mean some of I mean that's
another interesting part of your past
have you ever been incarcerated before
have I ever been incarcerated no not for
longer than a day long enough somebody
to take me you know the police can
arrest anybody want put him in jail but
if you stayed here that you know I'm
saying I haven't stayed anywhere I've
been arrested a lot putting to sell
they're coming at me when I call my
lawyer
you know but I mean it's a type of God
well I wanted to bring up obviously
tomorrow is a big day you've been
sentenced tomorrow and you know we're
sitting here in 24 hours you'll know
what you know what the situation is
going to be are you thinking about the
prospect of going to jail first I was
like I'm not going to jail I was like if
they try to come to get me for something
I didn't do I'm over fine you know I'm
saying but I can't do that because it's
not just me anymore you know I'm saying
that's what they expect if I have to if
God sees it fit for me to spend time in
itself he wants my brain to be inside of
a cage if he's bought me so far from
hell to put me here and now he wants me
to go to jail I'll go you know I'm
saying if that's why I'm meant to be but
I don't think so I don't think so no I'm
saying I don't really believe in my
heart that I belong in jail I don't
believe I did anything to warrant me
going to jail what do you think if you
do go to jail is to be expected because
you are a known person
i'ma ask to be put in solitary
confinement I'm gonna do push-ups and
read books and come out weed free smoke
free and with a degree or some shame I'm
saying I won't let it stop me you know
I'm saying but I'm not going to jail to
just part of that if I went to jail best
believe it's not like I'm gonna have a
problem in jail I got love there you
know I'm saying I got love from ducks
and the street dudes and I can go to
jail and probably organize a riot you
know it's sad but that's not what I want
to do if I have to go to jail I don't
even want to be living I want to just
cease to exist forever long that has me
there and then when I come out I'll be
reborn you know I'm saying I'd be taking
less less problems and like my mind I'd
be sharper and the venom will be more
potent you know I'm saying so they
shouldn't send me there they should
really try to Pete you know it's like
you don't don't want gasoline on the
fire to put it out what what about I
mean this is one step and there's some
other you know cases that are going to
be coming up what has changed for you
and you mentioned the last two years is
when everything started to happen one
after the other what changed for you in
these two years how is your life now
different than it was before like I said
you know it was no spot for Tupac it's
not like there was somebody like me
before and I mean I moved into the spot
so I can ask him how he did it you know
I'm saying there was no spottier nobody
wants to be you know the person that
Doug's in the street people corralling
around nobody wanted to be there so when
I was that I couldn't handle it you know
saying I couldn't I could handle it but
not right away
of course I have problems I was making
mistakes that anybody would make when
you have 14,000 people ready to do
whatever you want you know I'm saying
when you have all over the country
people waiting to hear what you want to
do you know I'm saying this thug life
coat we have a cold put your order to
the violence on the streets and when
they are listening to you I got people
in a penitentiary you know saying big
time old G criminals who are calling me
telling me they want me to lead their
movement I mean I'm gonna have a problem
you know say I'm gonna have a small
identity crisis here you know
saying because I like I said I was just
from a single father you know I mean a
single mother with no father no man
figure now I got every man in America
who wants to take a quarter from me you
know the saying wants to know what I
want to do or you know what's my plan
for young black males and that makes me
scared but that makes me want to rise to
the occasion you know I'm saying what
makes me want to give my whole life to
him and I will give my whole life to
this planet I have the thug lines
now when you set a code I don't know
exactly what do you mean by a code I
organized the OGS and East Coast and the
west coast and the penitentiaries to
come up with a set of codes of ethics
for criminals you know like we're going
to get big against drive-bys kidnappings
attacks on people that are not involved
with it with the street gang the drug
trade or the illegal businesses oh you
know I'll let kidnapping and shooting
drive-bys out the car we against that
and people who perpetrate that they have
to deal with the consequences when they
go to jail
cuz that's what's gonna enforce this
cold and the thug life that's on the
street it's like we cleaning up the dirt
I can't change what the dirt that's here
but I can put all this dirt in one
corner you know I'm saying somehow have
some order here and for that they need
to give me a little leg room you know
I'm saying let me need let me do what I
want to do because nobody else was gonna
do it nobody else wants to do it but I'm
not scared to walk in the middle of
watts Compton Chicago whatever sit down
with whoever's the og say this one we
need to do
you