I read in Billboard magazine today that
you have been struggling with you you
were diagnosed with lupus and that you
went through chemo is that right yes
when did this happen three years ago you
know and and I think it was just very
complicated cuz I didn't understand and
then that was something I did want to
keep private until my whole life
suddenly wasn't private right right so I
just kind of uh it was my it was my
moment I'm really honestly I'm able to
relate to people and I get it you know
and what what is I don't know what lupus
is what is it exactly can autoimmune
disease oh and are you do you still have
it or well yeah you'll have it forever
uh-huh it's kind of one of those
situations but just gonna take care of
yourself well that's a good thing to do
anyway so I'm glad you say you're good
hand right now hey I'm glad to hear it
yeah you were picked on there was a
picture you were you're on vacation
you're in a bikini
you look fantastic thank you this is the
picture that they said something about
that you were overweight or some cut
what did they say about this yeah uh
yeah it was the first time I had ever
been called fat unbelievable but it was
weird because it's not just oh she's fat
it's like she's a mess she's you know
she's got off the deep end I'm like cuz
I'm on a vacation where I could be
anything sir actually technically that
is a little too small for me but I
didn't care um I don't think they were
saying the bathing suit was small I'm
talking about you're fat they're saying
that you know it's so degrading but but
you know you own that and you you
tweeted something out saying look I
don't want them to win it's so annoying
when I see it all over the place and
everybody thinks they can bring me down
and so my immediate response was I'm
gonna post a picture and I'm like I'm
happy with Niall and that was gonna be
the story the next day I was
good
yeah yes you can always have the last
word if you choose to I mean sometimes
we don't want to address these things
cuz there's so many lies and I just
spent my whole career doing that yeah a
little bit yeah
it's so nice to be able to be like oh
yeah Karen yes where I am yeah good for
you I'm glad because it'sit's a lot for
you you're 23 right to be you know
scrutinized and analyzed and everybody's
saying what they think about you and
it's like you know just let you be a 23
year old girl and grow up and you know
be creative and be an artist and that's
important let's talk about your
boyfriend I have a boyfriend I don't
know do you who where that's how I
thought I'd set it up oh god I know some
I don't but if you have any
recommendations Oh short well when we
drink wine and talk about boys music and
oh I've been dating it's very it's very
it's fun are you dating
yeah how do you meet guys is it what you
have to meet people within the business
I mean I think that both yeah places
uh-huh and you know did our dating
you're dating now
yeah no I mean I've been on a few dates
and then they haven't gone anywhere I
mean yeah ish they've gone somewhere ish
yeah yeah but you haven't found a
boyfriend yet right
well Taylor should hook you up doesn't
she meet lots of she's got she's all
over the place
hey she's what about she's at the stud I
know I love him but I'm saying like
there must be all kinds of Sharia
service a list friend friends of his
yeah but it's weird cuz I don't know if
I want some buddies in the industry
who's not who kind of gets it who
doesn't I don't know yeah it's weird I
kind of want somebody in the industry
because you travel so much it's gonna be
hard for somebody to be at home like
selling life insurance this is a very
stressful conversation I'm not even
thinking about it we should be drinking
um while we're talking about boys