why do you want to be executed I have to
be
there's our world kill again no I would
do it again I've been molesting kids
non-stop since I was 13 years old over
half my life anything happened I can
guarantee I do it again and sooner or
later I would kill another child I've
done it before and at the time I liked
it
God also says that if he ever escapes
from prison there is someone in
particular that he will be able to kill
I'm not gonna say who but there is
somebody out there there's a man out
there there's a man yeah someone related
to the case that got you in prison in
the first place mmm not directly no but
it's something that you know that you're
going to do or you plan to do you want
to do yeah your execution do any good I
think it would I think a few child
molesters anyway are going to think
twice before they do anything again how
do you live with yourself
daily the times it's not easy I said
there's times I think about what I've
done I think about some of the things
the boys said before they died and and
that's real hard to think about at other
times they just try to put everything
out of my mind do you look forward to
dying
in a way yeah I could be a relief I
don't have to think about all these
things anymore I know that's the only
way I can guarantee I'm not gonna hurt
anybody else
you know right now I sit here and say I
don't want to but I know it'll happen
[Music]