have you offered him the role of brixon
secretary now I don't talk about things
to do with to do with the cabinet
cabinet reshuffle I happened to point at
a brexit snoo brexit secretary yet but
obviously I'll be doing that over the
course of the next day awesome Michael's
done a really important job at d'etre
and often people don't think about how
individual government departments are
having to prepare for leaving the
European Union actually Michael's
Department is the one that has you know
in terms of legislation probably more
preparation than anybody else he's been
doing a great job you do you consider
yourself the modern-day Chamberlain they
also went to Europe and ago she ate with
a foreign power and came back as having
a pedes that foreign power and have not
stood up for our country no I don't and
the reason is this we're not going to be
locked in forever to something that we
don't want what we're doing is
negotiating a deal that means that we
can take back control of our borders
free movement will end once and for all
that we take back control of our money
we won't be sending vast sums of money
to the EU every year address this point
the DUP will be voting with you know the
deep I when this vote comes back every
individual member of parliament will
decide how they vote whether they
remember the DUP conservative labor all
parties within the House of Commons my
job is to persuade you know first and
foremost my conservative benches those
who are working with us the DUP are
working with us obviously in confidence
and supply but I want to say be able to
say to all parliamentarians every MP I
believe this is truly believe this is
the best deal for Britain was Boris
Johnson Rachel stood by that bus two and
a bit years ago well this is this is a
commitment that the government is making
now yes we can get some money back from
the it's not actually it's 394 so he
wasn't right to stone was 394 million
that we will be putting extra that we
will be putting into the NHS per week
per week so he was right to stand by the
bus Boris Johnson for the point Boris
was making was and the point people in
the referendum was making was that if we
don't send vast amounts of money to EU
every year we can spend it on our
priorities back home we'll look happen
to get a free vote the we will be
obviously we're going to be looking at
the deal when it comes back there is
cabinet collective responsibility in
this country which you know this
government policy is government policy