airman are yous gotta be well clever to
run a massive business
I actually met Ronald McDonald and the
cousins 15th birthday party Onegin and
him even though he dressed like a total
prick is hacci genius if any can be the
head of a massive business so can i I'm
gonna find that out never had an idea
before how does you know when you had
one right how do you know when you say
wow you know for a business idea I mean
like eyes you know at the idea fly-in
chicken or right switched on to tell you
or something I've never had an idea
right for a business idea right well
whatever right you know if you had all
the money in the world this is a good
exercise yeah and you can do anything
with this money to you know to make your
life easier what's the first thing you
would invent like free that was a good
place it's always like you know just
stop for anything right okay and there's
uh that's what it could be a good
business um if we tell someone my idea
how does I know they aint gonna Nick it
um that stuff people usually do because
like when the PlayStation one came out
me was telling me Julie what would be
wicked would be if they brought out
something that was better than this
right and then two years later what come
out PlayStation 2 right how does you
think they got the idea from me maybe
Julie told them I don't know but but the
fact is that people eat foods and and if
she did well then yes yoga night you
talk to her yes serious sure cuz there's
something called trust absolutely
I've got some business idea that I just
want to tell you about and I'll be a
fool if very quickly what is the most
popular thing in the world music no tell
me ice cream
okay everyone has it and what is the
problem with ice cream I have no idea it
drips okay so me idea is what you to
make a drip proof ice cream no put in
our business
all right wafer you ain't gonna come out
with that though no I promise you I want
me IP is to come out with just like
these ice cream gloves that make the ice
cream not go on your hands and make it
well sticky and also keep your hands
warm look at when when you Izzy indie
ice cream okay is your winner is do it
okay well it sounds like a good idea and
I hope you make a lot of money
good luck folks it's been nice seeing
you you take care of yourself okay
you're gonna be in on that well it
sounds like an interest we just got that
P Diddy is gonna be in it good
it's ice cream to me eat this no okay
what's my there lay it on me the ice
cream glove
that's a C which means that you can't
Nick it alright and my me idea is you
could do them in like a favorite team
gloves colors just like the LA Lakers I
don't care what it looks like yeah
that's like what you what that to me I'm
not carrying around a glove in my pocket
so then the event I mean in ice cream
I'm taking a glove out of my pocket to
preserve my suit as you seen one of
these things before sure everyone in
school learns these things sure
zendaya grams sure people who like ice
cream people who wears hands chair
what's this section here this our target
market okay we did an internet search
for ice cream we come back with
sixty-two 6121 result we did it internet
search for the gloves
how much results did me get free 125 0
113 so you're times those together
what does you get this is just people on
the internet looking in 203 zillion
wherever four hundred ninety six
thousand four hundred and 1001 check
this out if all those people bought one
glove at 19,99
just one glove business would be worth
wait for it I'm waiting that much that
is such a big number couldn't fit it
that way that in English thirty four
point six million billion dollars how
does we promote this company we promote
it with the strongest image all right
you know money talks spoke all right
this may be this may be the worst idea
I've ever heard
I actually don't dislike the idea safe
respect yeah but it's a I don't dislike
the idea you can use it you know it's
not there's something to it this is not
gonna happen
I just got another business idea um okay
what is that what's this that is a
skateboard no is a toothbrush no let's
don't loose okay okay what is it
caught Brian what is it will tell you
what it is
it's a hoverboard
I don't understand what you mean it's a
hoverboard as you seen back to the
future
as you've seen the bit where if where
they jump on the board and it flies
around yeah it's in the future that feel
must have been about ten years ago no
one has even thought about making that
thing but it doesn't do that it doesn't
do it yet that's where you look coming
you come up with the science we don't do
that this is nothing it was it's a film
well they must have used the board from
somewhere they made one of them to work
so how did you jump on it and fly one
around and so what a chases then it's
not special effects how do they do
anything in a movie good luck
I'm gonna put on the glove before you
shake my hand good luck