Dean's insane calm chem you amber loss
so Manson sentence was commuted to life
in prison now there's a book
Manson in his own words as told to nil
Emmons chemins is an ex-con who first
met Manson while serving a short term in
prison for car theft and true to the
unwritten code of the underworld
Manson cooperated on the book because he
owed Emmons a favor today correspondent
Heidi Schulman went to talk with Manson
to find out after all these years is
there any remorse is he sorry does he
feel guilty well then we here on The
Today Show staff debated among ourselves
whether to air his answers half of our
staff said absolutely not even though
Manson doesn't make a cent off this book
let's not give him any publicity but
another half said yes believing that
some of you are as curious as some of us
are well at any rate here is what Manson
had to say Charles Manson is serving his
life sentence for murder in San Quentin
prison that is where we talked with him
and with Newell Emmons author of Charles
Manson in his own words our conversation
lasted an hour and a half during which
Manson was sometimes lucid sometimes
incoherent and frequently manipulative
from your words as mr. Evans quotes them
in this book it's clear that you were
guilty of murder and yet he says in all
his conversations with you he never
heard you express remorse have you never
felt it remorse for what you people have
done everything in the world to me
doesn't that give me equal right I can
do anything I want to you people at any
time I want to because that's what
you've done to me if you spit in my face
and smack me in the mouth and throw me
in solitary confinement for nothing what
do you thinks gonna happen when I get
out of here guilty
hmm I wouldn't do anything that I felt
guilty about you don't feel guilty at
all there's no need to feel guilty I
haven't done anything I'm ashamed of
maybe I haven't done enough I might be
ashamed of that for not doing enough for
not giving enough for not being more
perceptive for not being aware enough
for not understanding for be stupid
maybe I should have killed for 500
people then I would have felt better
then when I felt like I really offered
society something you know if I wanted
to kill somebody I'd take this book and
beat you to death with it and I wouldn't
feel a thing it'd be just like walking
to the drugstore do you feel brain are
you mad
do you feel like wounds kebab my friends
your friends boots pookajee pair remedy
gdb Google do you begin for Fabul
fighters ready to ISIL Braga Newell
Emmons is an ex-convict who first met
Manson in prison in the 50s
he claims he wrote the manson book after
seven years of conversation with Manson
to show that he's no leader no guru but
just a loser why should anyone care to
read this book
my purpose when I first started was
virtually to destroy the myth I show
that he's not as complex or as the cult
leader etcetera that he's been projected
as being I don't fit in society and I am
incompetent I'm definitely in confident
I would that well I say that I say that
there's nothing wrong with being
incompetent because you don't have to do
as much if you're confident then you got
a lot to do but there's there's it does
it there's another aspect of it too
I've learned to reflect I just reflect
back I know I don't know I know I'm
stupid I admit I'm a pity whatever I
never been a success at anything
I even got to the point where I didn't
want to be a success in anything what
would be in a success what does that
mean you know money I've had all the
money in the world three times and had
to give it back
that's a stupid little game you know my
awareness is my consciousness it's not
the same as somebody that goes to school
and has a mom and dad see not having
parents have left me in a another
dimension so to say you know I don't
have no bad going for nothing I don't
judge a Hollywood think about too much
it's hard for me remember breakfast in
fact if I didn't have two three girls to
help me I would pretty much be lost and
I wouldn't know what the hell I'm doing
you write in that in all your
conversations with Charles Manson he
never expressed remorse so have you seen
any today I may need perhaps he believes
totally in his own - it's not guilt guys
get too stuck in your head that I've
murdered somebody you've got it stuck in
your brain that I murdered somebody
well you want to call me a murderer for
I've never killed anyone I don't need to
kill anyone I think it I have it here
who is this man you've been talking to
for seven years well to me he's a
convict that was a failure I mean I mean
he's the person that is not capable I
mean and I still lay it - the way the
book reads it wasn't - start cleaning
the earth or anything I mean there was a
drug burn that initiated the first one
and the black guy the first
tone of violence at surfaced anyway and
then the death of Gary him and there
again it was dope related and it just
kept feeding from there and so it had no
spiritual aspects at all it was just a
bunch of guys out there kids out there
that was living doing their own thing
and it used to be party time and
playtime and then through drugs and the
whole bit will it started getting a
little bit nasty a little bit
and the first thing you know there's
murders and my whole life I've
fertilized the grocery stores sold some
nickels and dimes busted open and stamp
machine stole a few automobiles and
cashed a couple checks I'm a petty car
thief I've been with prostitutes and
bums and winos and all my life the
street is my world I don't I don't
pretend to go uptown and be anything
fancy I can but I find more real in the
world that I'm in then I do the tinsel
and the real world is the one I have to
deal with every day
you